pointclub.com 2016-01-14

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
Pointclub is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This privacy
protection section communicates how, when, and why we gather information about
our customers and what we do with it.
If you have any questions about the Pointclub.com privacy policies please contact us
at:
Pointclub Inc. 1410 Second Street, Suite 200, Santa Monica, CA
90401, admin@pointclub.com
This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites to which we link.
You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy.
If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use this Site.
Information Collected
If you subscribe to Pointclub and/or place an order through Pointclub.com, we will
ask you for your name, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number and
credit card information. We use this information to process and fulfill your order and
to notify you of your order status. All archived credit card information is maintained
in a secure and safe environment. Telephone numbers and e-mail addresses are used
to contact you regarding your order. Pointclub will never sell, rent or share your
personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for
marketing purposes without your express permission, or as described herein below. If
you decide to save your order information you will be creating an account that
includes a personal password. Please safeguard your password and other personal
information. You may be liable for unauthorized use of our web site, as well as have
your private information used by others. In addition, we automatically gather certain
information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site
are visited, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other
technologies. Most browsers can be set to prevent cookies or to notify you when one
is being placed. However, cookies are necessary to access the Site.
How We Use Your Information
We will not share or disclose your information to anyone except as described in this
Privacy Policy. We use personally identifiable information in order to give you a
more enjoyable convenient shopping experience and to help us identify and/or
provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your
personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and

its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer
service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the
Site. We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized
profile of your shopping history. In addition, we may notify you about new services
or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.
In connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and
certain features on the Site, certain trusted third parties may be permitted to access
your information. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site; operate
various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search
results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.
We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a
proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an
insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part
of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. In such a
circumstance the Transferee would be bound by the terms of this privacy policy.
We reserve the right to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena,
court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or
when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary in order to protect our rights
or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and
credit risk reduction.
We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can
improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or
share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no
personally identifiable information.
If you submit your email address to be added to a mailing list, we will use the email
address for the sole purpose of sending you announcements, special offers from
Pointclub and other partners along with site updates. Each email we send will contain
information on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list. You can also unsubscribe
by sending
an email to admin@pointclub.com
Your contact information (including but not limited to your name and email) will be
shared with the Science Launch Network ("SLN"), of which Pointclub is a member.
SLN may email you from time to time notifying you about new products and services
that they believe are relevant and interesting to you. You may opt out of SLN at any

time by emailing unsubscribeSLN@science-inc.com or by clicking on the
unsubscribe link in any email from SLN.
We use your feedback to improve our site and our organization. If you choose to
provide information about yourself using a feedback or email form on our Web site,
we will not use the information for any purpose other than to respond to your
inquiry or to act on your suggestion or comment. We will not share your information
with others except with your permission or upon your request.
Comments you voluntarily post on public forums such as our blog will, of course,
be displayed publicly along with the name you submit and the time at which you
submitted the comment.
If you elect to use our referral services for informing a friend about our site, we
ask you for the friend's name and email address. Pointclub will automatically send
the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site.
Pointclub stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email
and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Pointclub
at to request the removal of this information from our database.
How We Protect Your Information
We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow
reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality,
security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is
completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the
likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.
The Site encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using
secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the
information from your PC to our servers. In addition, only those employees and
third parties who need access to you information in order to perform their duties are
allowed such access.
Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences If you are a
registered user, you may access and update your registration information and your
preferences to receive email or other communications from us by sending an email
to
You may also update or change your personal information or preferences by sending
email to admin@pointclub.com. We will take commercially reasonable steps to

implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications
from us for up to ten business days as we process your request.
While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of your
information, we reserve the right to delete all or any portion of customer
information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.
Children’s Privacy and Parental Controls
We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older,
you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental
control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from
submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing
material that is harmful to minors.
Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised
Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how
we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your
continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.
